beyondtherack.com 2019-12-23

# Privacy

Effective Date: 07/08/2014

Last Updated on 03/02/2017   
  
Beyond the Rack is owned and operated by 9721444 Canada Inc. Your privacy is important to Beyond the Rack . So we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions by either: 

  * Emailing our Customer Service team at [privacy@beyondtherack.com](mailto:privacy@beyondtherack.com), or

  * Calling our toll-free number at **1-844-400-4287** Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET or

  * Mailing to:

Privacy Matters  
c/o Beyond the Rack   
5440 Rue Pare,  
Mont-Royal, Quebec  
H4P 1R3, Canada

**Our Policy Regarding Your Privacy**

This privacy policy describes how Beyond the Rack (“BTR”) collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Website: [www.beyondtherack.com](http://www.beyondtherack.com/) (“the Website”) for your use of the services or when you purchase products from BTR, features and content offered by Beyond the Rack (collectively referred to as the “BTR Services”). It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of your personal information and how you can access and update your personal information. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to "Beyond the Rack" include beyondtherack.com and BTR. 

**Identity and information protection**

Beyond the Rack is committed to protecting all the information you share with us. We follow stringent procedures to help protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of data stored on BTR systems.   
  
Only those employees who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed such access. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.   
  
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

**Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect online. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit or Visa Debit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).   
  
We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Please note, however, that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on the Website, you can contact us at [security@beyondtherack.com](mailto:security@beyondtherack.com).   

If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should first contact Customer Service. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at :   
https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request 

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us either by: 

  * Emailing our Customer Service team at [privacy@beyondtherack.com](mailto:privacy@beyondtherack.com), or

  * Calling our toll-free number at 1-844-400-4287 Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET, or

  * Mailing to:

Privacy Matters  
c/o Beyond the Rack  
5440 Rue Pare,  
Mont-Royal, Quebec  
H4P 1R3, Canada

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE GATHER ABOUT YOU?**

The information Beyond the Rack gathers falls into two categories: 

  1. Personally identifiable information, which includes personal information you supply when you register, order, complete a survey, enter a contest, provide your email address or provide your friends’ emails addresses and

  2. Non-personally identifiable information collected through technology, which includes tracking information collected as you navigate the Website.

_**Personally Identifiable Information That You Provide Us**_

**Registration**

Registration for the BTR Services requires that you supply certain personally identifiable information, including, in most cases, your first name, your last name, a unique email address and a password to register. This allows BTR to provide you access to your account every time you visit the Website. Beyond the Rack keeps track of your information to offer you the best possible shopping experience. 

**Paid Products and Services**

To enable the purchase of products, we also collect and store billing and credit/Visa Debit card information as well as your address, telephone number or any other information required to process your order.   
  
This information may be disclosed to specific members of our staff and to select third parties (such as our credit/Visa Debit card processor and shipping provider) involved in the completion of your transaction and delivery of your order. Examples of this include fulfilling orders and processing credit or Visa Debit card payments service providers.   
  
We will also use your email address and/or telephone number to notify you about new services, special promotional programs, promotional offers or any information related to BTR Services.   
  
At any time, you can notify us that you wish to stop receiving these emails or telephone calls by either: 

  * Making the appropriate selections in your account management center, or

  * Following the "unsubscribe" instructions located near the bottom of each email, or

  * Contacting us at [unsubscribe@beyondtherack.com](mailto:unsubscribe@beyondtherack.com) requesting that we remove your email and/or telephone number from our database. To do so please include your email and/or telephone number in the body of your email, and put "Unsubscribe" in the subject line, or

  * Calling our toll-free number at **1-844-400-4287** Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET.

In addition, we keep a record of your past purchases, returns, and credits. We may also ask you for information regarding your personal preferences and demographics to better meet your needs. 

**Personal Information about Children**

The Website is targeted for use by a general audience; BTR does not market to or create special areas for use by children. Accordingly, BTR does not collect age identifying information nor does BTR knowingly collect any personal information, even in aggregate, from children under the age of 13 years. However, we hereby advise all visitors to the Website under the age of 13 not to disclose or provide any personally identifiable information on the Website. In the event that we discover that a child under the age of 13 has provided personally identifiable information to BTR, in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protect Act ([see the Federal Trade Commission's website](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html)), we will delete the child's personally identifiable information from our files and databases to the extent technologically possible.

**Registration to the Website via Third-Party Tools**

You may choose to log-on, create an account or enhance your profile at beyondtherack.com with the Facebook Connect feature on the Website. By doing this, you are asking Facebook to send us registration information from your Facebook profile. We treat that information as we do any other information you give to us when you log on, register or create a profile. After you have connected, Facebook also sends us additional information from your profile that allows us to display a Facebook module on the pages you view. We do not store this additional information. 

**Social Media Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Contests, Sweepstakes and Special Offers**

Beyond the Rack collects personal information such as your first name, your last name, a unique email address and a password from readers in connection with optional sweepstakes, contests or special offers. If this information is to be shared with a third party other than Beyond the Rack, we will notify you at the time of collection. If you do not want any personal information shared, you may always decline to participate in the sweepstakes, contest or special offer.

**Members Surveys**

Beyond the Rack may collect personal information such as your first name, your last name, a unique email address and a password as well as your opinion on specific BTR services from members in connection with voluntary surveys. Data may be collected on the Website, on the phone or through the mail. The information you provide by answering optional survey questions may be shared, but only in the aggregate, with advertisers and partners unless we notify you otherwise at the time of collection. 

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personal identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our services, you may correct, update, delete/deactivate it by either: 

  * Making the necessary changes in your member information page, or

  * Emailing our Customer Service team at [privacy@beyondtherack.com](mailto:privacy@beyondtherack.com), or

  * Calling our toll-free number at 1-844-400-4287 Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET or

  * Mailing to:

Privacy Matters  
c/o Beyond the Rack   
5440 Rue Pare,  
Mont-Royal, Quebec  
H4P 1R3, Canada

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Invite-A-Friend**

BTR uses SociableLabs to operate our referral program. Notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, Personal Information may be securely transferred to SociableLabs or other third parties in the context of the referral program, but only to the extent needed for the referral program to operate properly. This transfer of Personal Information is described in the next paragraph of this section. By using the referral program, you consent to our use of your Personal Information in this manner. If you do not consent to the use of your Personal Information in this manner, please do not use the referral program.   
  
The referral program will access your web-based email service (currently limited to Gmail, Hotmail, Yahoo or AOL). If you are not otherwise logged-in to the email service, it may ask you for your password in order to log in. Your password is not stored by either us or SociableLabs, and is only transferred securely to your email provider in order to log in for the referral program to function. The referral program will access your contacts from your email program, and may ask for your authorization to do so. No emails are sent to your contacts without your consent, as you must confirm to which email addresses you send a referral. Use of your email service is also governed by your email provider’s Terms of Use and / or Privacy Policy.   
  
When you share a link through the referral program via Facebook or Twitter, if you are not otherwise logged in, you may be asked for your login information, and your login information is transferred securely to those services. Your use of these services is covered by their respective Terms of Use and / or Privacy Policies.   
  
BTR and SociableLabs are in full compliance with both the U.S. CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (15 U.S.C. Ch. 103) and the Canadian law Informally known as Canada’s Anti-Spam Law (“CASL”, S.C. 2010, c. 23) within the referral program. BTR As part of our referral program, emails are sent which are subject to anti-spam laws, including the U.S. CAN-SPAM Act and Canada’s Anti-Spam Law. As these laws have different requirements based on the email recipient’s home country, it is important to distinguish your recipients. By using the referral program, you acknowledge that if you are using the American version of the website and referral program, you are sending to American recipients. If you are using the Canadian version of the website and referral program, you are sending to Canadian recipients.  
  
If you believe you have been sent an email in error or in violation of these laws OR your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database by either:   
  
Making the necessary changes in your member information page, or   
  
Emailing our Customer Service team at [service@beyondtherack.com](mailto:service@beyondtherack.com), or   
  
Calling our toll-free number at 1-844-400-4287 Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET or,   
  
Mailing to: 

Privacy Matters  
c/o Beyond the Rack  
5440 Rue Pare,  
Mont-Royal, Quebec  
H4P 1R3, Canada

Furthermore you can prevent any future referral emails from BTR by clicking the unsubscribe link in any invitation email you received. 

**Send Product as a Gift**

You have an option to send a product as a gift. In this case, we will also collect your recipient’s name, shipping address and phone number so we can send out your gift. Your recipient may contact us to request that we remove their information in our database through the same contact information mentioned above. 

**Compliance with Legal Process**

We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the BTR Services; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).   
  
**_Non-Personally Identifiable Information Collected Using Technology_**

**Information Collected by Us Using Technology**

Device Information: We may collect information about the computer, mobile telephone, smartphone or other device you use to access the Website. 

**Information Collected by Third Parties Using Technology**

Some of the services and advertisements included in the BTR Services, including on beyondtherack.com, are delivered or served by third-party companies that may place or recognize cookies, Web beacons or other technology to track certain non-personally identifiable information about the Website users. For example, in the course of serving certain advertisements, some advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser in order to collect certain information about your use of the BTR Services. In many cases, this information could be used to show you ads based on your interests on other websites.   
  
Please note that we do not have access to, nor control over, advertisers' or service providers' cookies or how they may be used. 

**Cookies**

The Website also transmits non-personally identifiable Website usage information about visitors to the servers of reputable third parties. To do this, BTR uses Web Beacons in conjunction with cookies provided by our third-party ad server vendors.  
  
The purpose is to recognize you, provide personalization, improve your shopping experience, save you time, help us understand where our visitors are going and how much time they spend there, as well as to target internet banner advertisements on other sites. You will not be able to access certain areas of the Website, if your computer does not accept cookies from beyondtherack.com.   
  
A cookie is a small piece of information that is stored on a computer for the purpose of identifying that browser during interaction on the websites. Cookies may be used to store items such as identifiers and user preferences. A website may set a cookie to the browser if the browser's preferences allow it. A browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has set, not those set by other websites.   
  
A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your computer for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following the directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. If you reject cookies, you may still use the Website, but your ability to use some areas of the Website may be limited.   
  
BTR uses third party vendors to store cookies on your computer when you first visit the Website in order to enable BTR to recognize you each time you come back to the Website. Our third party vendors use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. Through cookies BTR can customize the Website to your individual preferences in order to create a more personalized and convenient user experience.   
  
Please note that cookies stored on your computer through the Website or BTR email campaigns do not store personally identifiable information about you or your finances. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to the Website.   
  
For example, Google is one of the companies that serve advertisements for beyondtherack.com. The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the Website and across the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences)  
  
You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Alternatively, you may opt out of third-party vendors use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and by visiting [TRUSTe](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/)  
  
We also use Google conversion tracking to measure the conversion rate related to our Google AdWords campaigns. This allows Google to tell us how users find the Website using Google. To protect the user's privacy Google’s cookie is not personally-identifiable and expires in 30 days. If you want to disable conversion tracking cookies, you can set your browser to block cookies from the googleadservices.com domain. Please refer to the [Google Advertising and Privacy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/) for more information about Google Conversion Tracking and the ability to opt out.  
  
You have choices about the collection of information by third parties on the Website: 

  1. If you would like more information about advertisers' use of cookies, and about your option not to accept these cookies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

  2. If you would like to opt-out of having interest-based information collected during your visits to this Website or other sites, please [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

Your access to the Website will not be affected if you do not accept cookies served by third parties.   
  
If you don’t want Facebook to show you ads based on your activity on an advertiser’s websites or apps, opt-out below:   

Web Beacons

A web beacon is an object that is embedded in a web page or e-mail and is usually invisible to the user but allows checking that a user has viewed a specific page of the Website or e-mail.   
  
BTR and our third party advertising partner employ a tracking technique called web beacons. Web beacons can be small (usually 1×1 pixel) transparent GIF or PNG with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, embedded in an HTML page, usually a page on the web or the content of an e-mail, used to know if a user has completed a specific action like registering or placing an order. We do not tie the information gathered by web beacons to our customers’ personally identifiable information.   
  
We use web beacons in our HTML-based emails to know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows BTR to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please proceed by either: 

  * Making the appropriate selections in your account management center, or

  * Following the "unsubscribe" instructions located near the bottom of each email, or

  * Contacting us at [unsubscribe@beyondtherack.com](mailto:unsubscribe@beyondtherack.com) requesting that we remove your email from our database. To do so please include your email in the body of your email, and put "Unsubscribe" in the subject line, or

  * Calling our toll-free number at 1-844-400-4287 Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET.

Analytics Technologies: BTR uses third party tools to collect information, reports and analysis about the usage, browsing patterns of users of the Website.  
  
BTR uses this data to make improvements to your shopping experience and to ensure that the Website has enough capacity to properly serve all of our users. The software provides aggregate reporting information to Beyond the Rack only. No personal or personally identifiable information is gathered or used for this process.  
  
The Website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies" to help the Website analyze how users use the Website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on its servers. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Website, compiling reports on Website activity for Website operators and providing other services relating to Website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Website. By using the Website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. 

**WHAT DO WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER ABOUT YOU?**

**Providing the Services You Request**

We use the information we gather about you to enable your use of the BTR Services. 

**Statistical Analysis**

We perform statistical, demographic and marketing analyses of users of the BTR Services, and their subscribing and purchasing patterns, for product development purposes and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our subscriber base. Beyond the Rack uses this information for analysis purposes, including analysis to improve customer relationships. 

**Customizing Your Experience**

We use the information that we collect to allow advertising to be targeted to the users for whom such advertising is most pertinent. We also use this information to customize certain features of the BTR Services to provide you with an enhanced experienced based on the type of device you are using to access the BTR Services, and in certain cases, provide you with requested services. 

**Relevant Advertising**

We may use demographic and preference information to allow advertising on the BTR Service to be targeted, in aggregate, to the users for whom they are most pertinent. This means users see advertising that is most likely to interest them, and advertisers send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer's experience and the effectiveness of the ads. We disclose information to third parties only in aggregate form. 

**Email**

BTR will periodically send you promotional emails about services offered by Beyond the Rack. For details about Beyond the Rack’s mail policy, please see the section labeled "Email and Telephone Policy" below. 

**Telephone Number**

BTR will periodically call you to explain emails about services offered by Beyond the Rack. For details about Beyond the Rack’s telephone policy, please see the section labeled "Email and Telephone Policy" below. 

**WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE THE INFORMATION THAT WE GATHER?**

**Beyond the Rack**

If you have registered to use the BTR Services, we will not sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your email address or any information that personally identifies you. We do, however, share information about our audience in aggregate form.

**Service Providers**

We contract with other companies to provide services on our behalf, including hosting the Website, operating various features made available on the Website, sending emails, analyzing data, providing search results and links, credit-card and payment processing, shipping, email distribution, list processing and analytics, customer service through live chat software, order fulfillment or promotions management.   
  
We provide these companies only with the information they need to perform their services. These service providers are restricted by BTR from using this data in any way other than to provide services for Beyond the Rack, and they may not share or resell this data.   
  
We contract with other providers to provide advertising to BTR’s customers in the aggregate without disclosing personal information.   
  
We reserve the right to disclose your unsubscribe information to third parties so they can suppress your name from future solicitations, in accordance with applicable laws. We may occasionally release personal information as required by law, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena.

**Email and Telephone Policy**

**Beyond the Rack complies fully with the federal CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, the Canadian Fighting Internet and Wireless Spam[Bill C-28](http://www2.parl.gc.ca/sites/lop/legisinfo/index.asp?Language=E&Chamber=N&StartList=A&EndList=Z&Session=23&Type=0&Scope=I&query=7019&List=toc-1), and the federal Internet and Wireless Spam [Bill C-28](http://www2.parl.gc.ca/sites/lop/legisinfo/index.asp?Language=E&Chamber=N&StartList=A&EndList=Z&Session=23&Type=0&Scope=I&query=7019&List=toc-1)** **.** We will not share, sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your email address or telephone number without your permission. If you feel you have received an email or telephone call from us in error, please contact us at: [privacy@beyondtherack.com](mailto:privacy@beyondtherack.com).  
  
 **Account and Service-Related Email:** Beyond the Rack reserves the right to send you emails relating to your account status. This includes order confirmations, notices of credit-card problems, other transactional emails and notifications about major changes to the BTR Services. 

**Promotional Email:** BTR may periodically email you messages or call you to explain about products and services that we think may be of interest to you. You can choose not to receive messages in the future by either: 

  * Making the appropriate selections in your account management center, or

  * Following the "unsubscribe" instructions located near the bottom of each email, or

  * Contacting us at [unsubscribe@beyondtherack.com](mailto:unsubscribe@beyondtherack.com) requesting that we remove your email and/or telephone number from our database. To do so please include your email in the body of your email, and put "Unsubscribe" in the subject line, or

  * Calling our toll-free number at **1-844-400-4287** Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET.

**Survey Email** : BTR may send you an email inviting you to participate in user surveys, asking for feedback on BTR Services and existing or prospective products and services, as well as information to better understand our users. User surveys greatly help us to improve BTR Services, and any information obtained in such surveys will not be shared with third parties, except in aggregate form.  
  
 **HTML Email:** When you sign up to receive emails from us, you can select either plain text or HTML (with images) format. If you select the HTML format, we may place a one-pixel gif to determine whether or not you have viewed the email. This process does not leave any information on your computer, nor does it collect information from your computer. Beyond the Rack may share this data with others in aggregate form only.   
  
**Emails from You:** If you send us emails, you should be aware that information disclosed in emails may not be secure or encrypted and thus may be available to others. We suggest that you exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal or confidential information in emails. We will use your email address to respond directly to your questions or comments.   
  
If, at any time, you prefer not to receive promotional emails, traditional mail or telephone solicitations originated by Beyond the Rack and its third party affiliates, you can choose not to receive messages in the future by either: 

  * Making the appropriate selections in your account management center, or

  * Following the "unsubscribe" instructions located near the bottom of each email, or

  * Mailing to:

Privacy Matters  
c/o Beyond the Rack  
5440 Rue Pare,  
Mont-Royal, Quebec  
H4P 1R3, Canada

  * Contacting us at [unsubscribe@beyondtherack.com](mailto:unsubscribe@beyondtherack.com) requesting that we remove your email from our database. To do so please include your email in the body of your email and put "Unsubscribe" in the subject line, or

  * By Calling our toll-free number at 1-844-400-4287 Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET.

**Reading History**

BTR automatically logs certain usage information about your use of the Website. This information includes a reading history of the pages you view. We use this information in order to provide you with customized recommendations on beyondtherack.com. We also use log files in the aggregate to analyze usage of the Website. 

**Log files**

In an effort to make the Website as effective and enjoyable as possible, the computers that operate the Website use third party tracking services to collect certain information each time you visit the Website. We store these statistics in log files. Once again, these statistics do not identify you personally, but provide us information regarding the type of users who are accessing the Website and certain browsing activities of those users. This data may include: the IP address of the user accessing the Website (i.e. the unique I.D. number of the user's computer), the type of browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, etc.), the operating system (Windows, Mac OS, etc.), the Website the user last visited before linking to the Website, how long the user accessed the Website in any given session, and the date and time of access. We may make extensive use of this data at an aggregated level in order to understand how the Website is being used. We may share some of the aggregate findings (not the specific data) with advertisers, sponsors, investors, strategic partners, and others in order to help grow our business. 

**HOW DO I CHANGE OR UPDATE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

**BTR Web Account:** You may update and/or edit your BTR account information online on the Website. Should you require assistance, please call us toll-free number at **1-844-400-4287** Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET.   
  
**Manage Your beyondtherack.com Account at Member Center:** You may review and update your beyondtherack.com account information and access your transaction history in the Member Center by logging at [www.beyondtherack.com](http://www.beyondtherack.com/).   
  
To gain access to the Member Center, you will be asked to enter your password. If you do not remember your password, you can request it by using the “Forgot Password” functionality. If you need further assistance, please contact Customer Service by email at [service@beyondtherack.com](mailto:service@beyondtherack.com) or By Calling our toll-free number at **1-844-400-4287** Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET.   
  
There are a number of things you can do in the Member Center to ensure your personal information is accurate and up to date. 

  1. You can update the information provided during the registration process. You may securely update your first and last name; email and shipping address, phone, and password registered on the account and provide us some basic demographic data.

  2. You can also subscribe or unsubscribe from Beyond the Rack’s periodic events emails, by clicking on the “Notifications” sub tab and unchecking the email notifications that you do not want to receive anymore and clicking "UPDATE."

  3. You can also track your orders by selecting the “Track Orders” tab.

  4. Finally you also have the ability to invite your friends to join BTR by clicking the “INVITATIONS” tab to get a $10.00 credit for each friend that purchases an item through the Website.

**HOW DO I UNSUBSCRIBE FROM RECEIVING PROMOTIONAL OFFERS?**

**Email**  
  
If, at any time, you prefer not to receive email marketing information and/or telephone calls from us, please proceed by either: 

  * Making the appropriate selections in your account management center. [Click here](http://www.beyondtherack.com/) to log in to your Beyond the Rack account. Click on the "Account" section at the top of the navigational bar and proceed to the "NOTIFICATIONS" section. On the “NOTIFICATIONS” page please uncheck the email notifications that you want to unsubscribe from and click "UPDATE", or

  * Following the "unsubscribe" instructions located near the bottom of each email, or

  * Mailing to:

Privacy Matters  
c/o Beyond the Rack   
5440 Rue Pare,  
Mont-Royal, Quebec  
H4P 1R3, Canada

  * Contacting us at [unsubscribe@beyondtherack.com](mailto:unsubscribe@beyondtherack.com) requesting that we remove your email and/or telephone number from our database. To do so please include your email in the body of your email and put "Unsubscribe" in the subject line, or

  * Calling our toll-free number at 1-844-400-4287 Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET.

**Links to Other Sites**

The Website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Beyond the Rack. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit. 

**Testimonials**

With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your first name.   
  
The testimonials presented on the Website are applicable to the individuals depicted and may not be representative of the experience of others.  
  
The testimonials are not paid and are not indicative of future performance or success.   
  
We reserve the right to choose which testimonials will be published on the Website or in advertising materials.   
  
If you want your testimonial to be removed please contact us at [testimonials@beyondtherack.com](mailto:testimonials@beyondtherack.com) and we will remove it as soon as reasonably possible.  
  
We may edit your testimonial for errors such as spelling and grammar prior to adding it to the Website or to any advertising material.   
  
In order to protect your privacy, we do not include surnames and/or family names with testimonials. 

Public Forums

The Website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [service@beyondtherack.com](mailto:service@beyondtherack.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**Exceptions**

Beyond the Rack may be forced to disclose information in order to comply with a subpoena, court order, administrative or governmental order, or any other requirement of law, or when Beyond the Rack, in its sole discretion, deems it necessary in order to protect our rights or the rights of others, to prevent harm to persons or property, to fight fraud and credit risk, or to enforce or apply the Website terms of use. Personally identifiable information may be transferred as an asset in connection with a merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale, or other change in control. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information. 

**Changes in policy**

You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of the Terms of Use and you unconditionally agree that using this Website signifies your assent to Beyond the Rack's Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. Your visit and any dispute over privacy matters are subject to this policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages. Beyond the Rack reserves the right to change the terms of use and this Privacy Policy, at any time. We will post any changes on the Website prior to the change becoming effective so that you are always aware of our Privacy Policy, so please make sure to check back periodically. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make and we will never change our policies and practices to make them less protective of you personally identifiable information without your consent. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy please let us know by either: 

  * Emailing our Customer Service team at [privacy@beyondtherack.com](mailto:privacy@beyondtherack.com), or

  * Calling our toll-free number at **1-844-400-4287** Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET.

  * Mailing to:

Privacy Matters  
c/o Beyond the Rack  
5440 Rue Pare,  
Mont-Royal, Quebec  
H4P 1R3, Canada

**TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SALE - CANADA**

**1\. Definitions**

"Seller" means Beyond the Rack Enterprises Inc., whose registered office is at 905 rue Hodge, Saint-Laurent, Quebec, Canada H4N 2B3.  
  
"Buyer" means the person who purchases Goods from the Seller.  
  
"Faulty" means containing a fault or defect, imperfect or defective, and "Fault" has a corresponding meaning.  
  
"Goods" means the goods or services which the Seller sells to the Buyer.  
  
"Order" means the Buyer's offer to purchase Goods from the Seller, as submitted by the Buyer to the Seller via the Order page on the Website.  
  
"Order Confirmation" means the Seller's written confirmation that it will sell Goods to the Buyer in accordance with an Order from the Buyer.  
  
"Purchase Price" means the price to be paid by the Buyer for the Goods, as set out in the Order Confirmation, and any applicable sales, use, excise, goods and services / harmonized and other taxes, freight, shipping and handling.  
  
"Sales Event" means the time period which begins at such time and date determined by the Seller where the Seller advertises a particular Good on the Website or otherwise and is accepting Orders for such Good, and ending on the time and date determined by the Seller where the Seller stops accepting Orders for such Good.  
  
"Special Conditions" are any terms and conditions imposing additional restrictions, obligations and/or conditions on any Orders that are set out in the Order Confirmation.  
  
"Terms and Conditions" means these terms and conditions of sale, the Order Confirmation, including any Special Conditions and any policy referred to herein.  
  
"Website" means beyondtherack.com and all pages on the website. 

**2\. Basis of Sale**

  1. To submit an Order, the Buyer must register for an account with us.

  2. By submitting an Order, the Buyer is bound by these Terms and Conditions.

  3. These Terms and Conditions and any document referenced herein form the entire agreement between the parties for the Ordering and the purchase and sale of Goods. The parties expressly exclude any other terms, including any terms and conditions which the Buyer may purport to add to any Order or other document. To the extent that any provision in Buyer's Order or other document purports to supplement, amend or delete any provision in these Terms and Conditions, such provisions shall be deemed to be void, excluded and are not binding on the Seller.

  4. Any variation of these Terms and Conditions by the Buyer will only bind the Seller if agreed in writing between authorized representatives of the Seller and the Buyer and further provided that such writing specifically references this Section of these Terms and Conditions.

  5. The Seller's employees are not authorized to make any representations, warranties or conditions concerning the Goods unless confirmed by the Seller in writing. The Buyer acknowledges that it does not rely on representations concerning the Goods which are not confirmed in this way.

**3\. Orders and Acceptance**

  1. Buyer may submit an Order to Seller during a Sales Event. Seller has the sole discretion to determine the beginning, duration and end of all Sales Events. Seller may terminate a Sales Event at any time, in its sole discretion.

  2. All Orders are subject to acceptance by the Seller, evidenced as the Seller issuing an Order Confirmation. The Buyer's Order constitutes an offer to purchase Goods at the Purchase Price in accordance with these Terms and Conditions, and is not binding on the Seller unless and until the Seller has issued an Order Confirmation. The Buyer may cancel an Order, even if an Order Confirmation has been received, prior to the end of the Sales Event. The Buyer cannot cancel an Order for any reason after the end of the Sales Event.

  3. The Seller reserves the right to reject the Buyer's Order in whole or in part without any liability to the Buyer, for any reason or for no reason, as determined by the Seller in its discretion, including if the Goods are unavailable due to unforeseen circumstances (including Orders exceeding reasonably anticipated demand), or are in imperfect condition at the expected time of shipment.

  4. The Seller may reject or cancel an Order for which an Order Confirmation has been issued for the following reasons: 

    1. The advertised price and/or Purchase Price on the Website, the Order and/or the Order Confirmation is incorrect due to a typographical error, failure to update, or inaccurate information received by the Seller from any person, including the Buyer or for any other reason;

    2. Orders received by the Seller for a particular Good exceed the Seller's reasonably anticipated demand;

    3. The description of the Goods on the Website, the Order and/or the Order Confirmation is incorrect due to a typographical error, failure to update, or inaccurate information received by the Seller from any person or for any other reason. All content on the Website, including any descriptions, specifications, drawings or prices of the Goods, is published for guidance only. The Buyer acknowledges that such information is provided to the Seller by third party manufacturers and that the Seller is not liable for mistakes in such information. Seller's sole remedy in such event is to return the Goods in accordance with the return procedure set out below.

  5. In the event of a rejection or cancellation as set out in Sections 3.3 or 3.4, the Seller has no liability or obligation to the Buyer whatsoever, including any obligation to source an alternate supplier of the Goods, find a replacement Good, and/or pay any consideration to the Buyer.

  6. The Seller may make minor modifications / substitutions in the design and specification of the Goods at any time without notice to the Buyer, even if an Order Confirmation has been issued. In the case of material modifications to the Goods, the Seller shall notify the Buyer of such material modifications. The Buyer may accept or reject the Good as modified within 48 hours of the email being sent by the Seller. If the Seller has not received a response from the Buyer within this time period, the Seller will refund the Purchase Price as per the original payment method(s) and cancel the Order, even if an Order Confirmation has previously been issued.

**4\. Advertised Price, Payment, Currency and Shipping**

  1. All advertised prices shown on the Website are exclusive of applicable sales, use, excise, goods and services / harmonized and other taxes, freight, shipping and handling. Any such fees and charges that are charged to or collected by the Seller are added to the advertised price, as shown in the Order Confirmation and are the responsibility of the Buyer.

  2. If the Goods are shipped to a location outside of Canada and the United States, there may be additional export/import duties, tariffs, charges, taxes and other fees which are levied on the Goods. The Buyer is responsible for payment of any such amounts. Please note that the Seller has no control over these amounts and cannot predict how much they will be. Please contact your local customs office for further information before placing your order.

  3. The Buyer will pay the Purchase Price in accordance with the procedures set out in the Seller's website.

  4. Payment is made by credit or Visa Debit card. The Seller will charge the Buyer's credit or Visa Debit card immediately upon acceptance of the Order and issuance of the Order Confirmation.

  5. The Buyer may redeem any existing credit on the Buyer's account towards the price of the Good, but not any applicable sales, use, excise, goods and services / harmonized and other taxes, freight, shipping and handling, provided that credits for Goods previously returned by the Buyer and accepted by the Seller may be applied towards the cost of freight, shipping and handling. All credits must be redeemed prior to the Buyer submitting the Order.

  6. Promotional credits (coupon codes and gift cards) expire 30 days from date of issue and must be used within that period, unless otherwise specified. Beyond the rack reserves the right to modify or cancel promotional credits at any time.

  7. All prices shown are U.S. dollars, other than for Buyers in Canada, for whom prices are shown in Canadian funds. Buyers in Canada will be charged in Canadian funds. All other Buyers will be charged in U.S. dollars. The Buyer is responsible for any variations and fluctuations in the exchange rate between U.S. dollars and Buyer's local currency and any exchange fees charged by Buyer's credit/debit card company.

**5\. Delivery**

  1. The place for delivery of the Goods will be set out on the Order Confirmation.

  2. Any dates quoted for delivery of the Goods are estimates only. Time for delivery will not be of the essence and the Seller will not be liable for any loss or expenses sustained by the Buyer arising from any delay in the delivery of the Goods howsoever caused.

  3. In the event that the quantity of Goods delivered is less than the quantity of Goods as indicated on the accompanying invoice or bill of lading, the Buyer shall accept the Goods delivered, shall note the shortage on the carrier's bill of lading, if possible, and shall notify the Seller of the shortage as set out in Section 5.5. For clarity, the Buyer may not reject the Goods or any part of them solely on the grounds of short delivery of an Order. The Buyer shall pay for such delivered Goods as if it was a delivery of an Order in installments (see Section 5.5).

  4. If the Goods are alleged to be damaged on delivery, a description of the alleged damage or Fault must be given in writing to the carrier at the time of delivery, if the alleged damage or Fault is obvious upon receipt. The Buyer must notify the Seller of the damage as set out Section 5.5.

  5. The Buyer must notify the Seller of any short delivery or Goods damaged in delivery, in writing, within three days of delivery. If the Buyer fails to do so within this time, the Goods are deemed to be delivered in good condition and in the quantities set out on the invoice and/or bill of lading. In each case, the notification must include the invoice number, Order Confirmation number, delivery note number and details of the claim. In the case of a valid claim for damaged Goods, the Seller may, in its sole discretion, replace the Goods (or the part in question) or refund to the Buyer the Purchase Price (or an appropriate proportion of the Purchase Price) exclusive of import/export or customs duties, tariffs, charges and/or other charges, as per the Buyer's original method(s) of Purchase. Damaged Goods must be returned to the Seller. In the case of a short shipment, other than a shipment that has been partially cancelled pursuant to Section 3.4, the Seller shall deliver the outstanding portion of the Order. In either case, the Seller will thereafter have no further liability to the Buyer for the short shipment or damaged Goods.

  6. The Seller reserves the right to make delivery of the Goods by installments, without notice to the Buyer.

  7. If the Buyer fails to take delivery of the Goods, the Seller may pursue any remedy legally available, including either or both of the following: 

    1. The Seller may store the Goods until actual delivery is effected and charge the Buyer for the cost (including insurance) of storage, together with any other reasonable incidental costs; and/or

    2. sell the Goods at the best price readily obtainable by the Seller and (after deducting all storage and selling expenses) charge the Buyer for any shortfall below the Purchase Price.

  8. The Buyer must advise the Seller in advance, in writing, of any requested alteration, cancellation or deferral of delivery, which the Seller may accept or reject at its discretion. The Seller reserves the right to make a charge (which will not normally be less than 20% of the cost of the Good altered, deferred or cancelled).

  9. Goods may not be returned to the Seller except as provided in Sections 7 and 8 below.

**6\. Risk and Property**

  1. Risk of damage to or loss of the Goods will pass to the Buyer on delivery at the address set out in the Order Confirmation.

  2. In the case where no signature or other proof of receipt is required by the carrier, all such Orders reported as delivered by the carrier shall be deemed to be delivered to and received by the Buyer. The Seller is not responsible for any lost or stolen Orders; the Buyer is solely responsible for selecting a secure delivery location.

  3. In the case where a signature or other proof of receipt is required by the carrier upon delivery, any signature on that document, or other proof of receipt, will constitute conclusive evidence of delivery of the Order to the Buyer.

**7\. Product Returns**

  1. The Buyer shall have the right to return Goods in the following circumstances: 

    1. for any reason, within one year(30 Days)beginning on the day after the Buyer receives the Goods, provided that this one year(30 Days) return period does not apply to: 

      1. Goods that cannot be accepted for return due to hygienic reasons (such as, but not limited to, toiletries, cosmetics and beauty products, lingerie, some leather goods, swimwear, earrings, duvets and pillows);

      2. Goods that have been made to the Buyer's specifications or personalized;

      3. Goods that been assembled or installed by or on behalf of the Buyer, in whole or in part;

      4. Goods that, by their nature cannot be returned, or are liable to deteriorate or expire rapidly; and

      5. Goods that are sold during "clearance" or "blowout" sales.

    2. within ten (10) days of delivery in the case of Faulty Goods (other than damage that is or should have been apparent upon delivery, which is subject to the three-day notification period set out in Section 5.5). Upon the Seller's confirmation that the Good is Faulty, the Seller will refund the Purchase Price as per the original payment method(s). However, this does not apply to Goods with a minor fault or defect, as determined by the Seller, that are capable of rectification, and are so rectified by the Seller at the Seller's cost. In the case of a minor fault or defect, the Seller may rectify the fault or defect by repair and/or a partial refund (as a BTR account credit), as determined by the Seller.

  2. Notice of the Buyer's wish to return the Goods must be made in accordance with the notice provision in Section 11.2 below. The return package must be postmarked within the return periods noted above.

  3. The Buyer must comply with the return procedure in Section 8 to obtain a BTR account credit. Failure to comply with such procedure will result in the Goods being rejected and returned to the Buyer.

  4. All Goods returned by the Buyer to the Seller must be the original Goods as delivered to the Buyer, in their original, undamaged packaging and must be in an unused condition (except only in the case of Goods which have been discovered to be Faulty).

  5. Under no circumstances will the Seller accept any returned Goods, even if Faulty, that have been tampered with, modified or replaced or switched with counterfeit and/or different products, in whole or in part, as determined by the Seller in its discretion. In such event, the Seller may reject the refund claim, retain the returned products, notify local law enforcement agencies in the Buyer's jurisdiction and/or pursue civil remedies against the Buyer.

  6. In the event that any return does not comply with these Terms and Conditions, the Seller reserves the right to refuse either all or some of the BTR account credit which would otherwise be due in respect of such returned Goods.

**8\. Procedure for Returned Goods**

  1. All returns must be made pursuant to the Returns Authorization procedure set out on the back of the packing slip.

  2. Provided that the Buyer has complied with these Terms and Conditions with respect to any returned Goods, the Seller shall issue a refund of the Purchase Price exclusive of any import/export or customs duties, tariffs, charges and/or other charges, subject to subsections 8.3 and 8.4 below). Refund shall be made by the issuance of a store credit to the Buyer's BTR account, other than for returns of Goods damaged on delivery or Faulty, in which case the Seller will refund the Purchase Price as per the original payment method(s). This provision of a BTR account credit is the Buyer's sole remedy for dissatisfaction with the Goods, including any claim that the Goods are Faulty or counterfeit.

  3. In the case of cancellation under Section 7.1.1 above, the Buyer is responsible for the costs of freight, shipping and handling and insurance to return the Goods to the Seller. If this is paid by the Seller, the Seller may deduct such amounts from any BTR account credit due to the Buyer (or to charge the Buyer, as the case may be).

  4. In the case of cancellation under Section 7.1.2 above, the Seller shall be responsible for freight, shipping and handling (including initial and re-delivery charges (if any)) in respect of the Goods, and shall refund the Purchase Price exclusive of any import/export or customs duties, tariffs, charges and/or other charges.

**9\. Warranties**

The Web site and products are provided “as-is” and as available and Beyond the Rack expressly disclaims any warranties and conditions of any kind, whether express or implied or collateral, including the warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular or general purpose, title, quiet enjoyment, accuracy, or non-infringement. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied warranties and conditions, so the above exclusion may not apply to you. The previous clause specifically does not apply to consumers in the province of Quebec. If applicable law requires implied warranties or conditions with respect to the products, then all such warranties or conditions are limited in duration to ninety (90) days from the date of purchase. If a supplier provides an express warranty, that warranty is between you and the supplier and not Beyond the Rack. Notwithstanding the foregoing, if a supplier of a product provides a warranty for the product and allows us to pass it through to you, we will pass it through to you. 

**10\. Limitation of Liability**

  1. Except as provided in Section 10.2, the Seller, its agents, employees, subcontractors and suppliers will not be liable to the Buyer for any indirect, incidental, special or consequential loss or damage, any loss of profit, loss of opportunity or revenue, or other claims for compensation whatsoever directly or indirectly arising out of or in connection with these Terms and Conditions, including any Order or Order Confirmation, including any failure or delay in performing any obligation hereunder, and/or including with the sale of the Goods or their use by the Buyer. Nothing in this Section 10.1 shall limit or exclude any liability of the Seller for death or personal injury caused by the Seller's negligence.

  2. The liability of the Seller, its agents, employees, subcontractors and suppliers with respect to any and all claims arising out of the performance or non-performance of the Seller's obligations in connection with these Terms and Conditions, including any Order or Order Confirmation, including any failure or delay in performing any obligation hereunder, and/or including with the sale of the Goods or their use by the Buyer, whether based on warranty, contract, negligence, strict liability or otherwise, shall not exceed, in the aggregate, the Purchase Price (excluding applicable sales, use, excise, goods and services / harmonized and other taxes, freight, shipping and handling) for such Goods. Such amount shall be the Buyer's sole remedy, and the Seller's sole liability for such matters.

  3. This limitation of liability shall prevail over any conflicting or inconsistent provision contained in any provision of these Terms and Conditions.

**11\. Notice**

  1. Any notice given or made under these Terms and Conditions will be in writing and delivered pursuant to Section 11.2 below.

  2. A notice will be deemed to have been duly given or made as follows: 

    1. if sent by personal delivery, including a nationally recognized courier (signature required upon receipt), upon delivery at the address of the receiving party;

    2. if sent by mail, five clear business days after the date of posting; or

    3. if sent by email, the first business day after mailing.

The foregoing time periods do not apply to emails sent by the Seller pursuant to Section 3.6 above, which notices shall be deemed to have been received immediately upon delivery. A "business day" means a day, other than a Saturday or a Sunday, during which the main branch in downtown Montreal of the Bank of Montreal is open for business during normal operating hours.

  3. For the purpose of these Terms and Conditions, notices will be given to the Seller at its address set out in Section 1, for the attention of the Company Secretary. Notices will be given to the Buyer at the address to which the Goods have been delivered.

  4. The Seller and the Buyer may notify each other of a change in their name, relevant addressee and address in accordance with this section. This notification will only be effective on: 

    1. the date specified as the date on which the change is to take place; or

    2. if no date is specified or the date specified is less than five clear business days after the date on which notice is given, the date falling five clear business days after notice of any change has been given.

**12\. Governing Law and Jurisdiction**

  1. To the extent permitted by law and except if restricted or prohibited by law, these Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the province of Quebec and the federal laws of Canada applicable therein without giving effect to the choice of laws provision thereof.

  2. The parties expressly exclude the operation of the United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods.

  3. These Terms and Conditions apply to the extent permitted by law and unless restricted or prohibited by law. The Buyer may have additional rights in its local jurisdiction that these Terms and Conditions cannot change. If any term or provision in the agreement is found to be void or unenforceable, including for reasons of being against public policy, by a court of competent jurisdiction, then the offending provision shall be deemed modified to the extent necessary to make it valid and enforceable. If the offending provision cannot be so modified (including if the court elects not to do so for any reason), then the same shall be deemed deleted in its entirety, and the remainder of these Terms and Conditions shall survive with the said offending provision eliminated.

  4. NOTHING IN THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SHALL OPERATE TO DENY OR LIMIT ANY RIGHTS OF, OR THE SELLER'S LIABILITY TO, ANY BUYER WHO IS A CONSUMER AS DEFINED PURSUANT ANY APPLICABLE LEGISLATION IN THE BUYER'S LOCAL JURISDICTION, WHICH RIGHTS SUCH BUYER MAY HAVE AT LAW. IN THE EVENT OF CONFLICT BETWEEN THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND ANY SUCH RIGHTS, THE LATTER SHALL PREVAIL IN FAVOR OF THE BUYER.

**13\. Intellectual Property**

  1. The Beyondtherack.com logo, name, and other marks indicated on the Website are trade-marks and/or registered trade-marks of Beyond the Rack, Limited in the Canada, the United States and/or other jurisdictions. Beyondtherack.com's graphics, logos, page headers, button icons, scripts and service names are the trade-marks or trade dress of Beyondtherack.com. Beyondtherack.com's trade-marks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not Beyondtherack.com's, in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers or in any manner that disparages or discredits Beyondtherack.com. All other trade-marks not owned by Beyondtherack.com that appear on this website are the property of their respective owners, who may or may not be affiliated with, connected to, or sponsored by Beyondtherack.com.

**14\. The Buyer is the end user of goods**

The Buyer agrees that all purchases are for personal use and will not be resold to other persons for any reason whatsoever. 

**15\. Copyright Complaints**

  1. User acknowledges that Beyondtherack.com is a "service provider" under the United States Digital Millennium Copyright Act (the "DMCA") and is therefore immune from liability under the DMCA. Consistent with the DMCA, Beyondtherack.com may accommodate standard technical measures used to identify and protect copyrighted works.

  2. Beyondtherack.com respects the intellectual property of others. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide Beyondtherack.com's copyright agent with the following information: 

    * An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest;

    * Description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;

    * The location of the material that you claim is infringing is located on the Beyondtherack.com website;

    * Your address, telephone number, and e-mail address;

    * A statement that your claim of infringement is based on a good-faith belief;

    * A statement made under penalty of perjury, that the information you have provided is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner's behalf.

**16\. Miscellaneous**

  1. No Waiver. If the Seller does not exercise a right or power when it is able to do so, this will not prevent it from later exercising that right or power. When it does exercise a right or power it may do so again in the same or a different manner. The Seller's rights and remedies are additional to and not in derogation of, any other rights and remedies it may have at law.

  2. Headings. Condition and section headings are for convenience of reference only and shall not affect the interpretation of these Terms and Conditions.

  3. English Language. The parties hereto confirm that it is their wish that this Agreement, as well as all other documents relating hereto, including all notices, have been and shall be drawn up in the English language only. Les parties aux présentes confirment leur volonté que cette convention, de même que tous les documents, y compris tout avis, qui s'y rattachent, soient rédigés en langue anglaise.

**17\. Privacy**

The Buyer consents to the collection, use and disclosure of the Buyer's personal information by the Seller and its third party providers and distributors in accordance with the terms and for the purposes set forth in the Privacy Policy at [www.beyondtherack.com/info/privacy](http://www.beyondtherack.com/info/privacy), the terms of which are hereby incorporated by reference. The Buyer agrees that the terms of such policy are reasonable. 

**18\. Emails and Telephone Calls**

Beyond the Rack and its affiliates reserve the right to send you communications electronically either via email, via site postings, or via telephone messages. You agree that all notices, agreements, disclosures and other communications that are provided to you electronically or by phone satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing. Should the user wish to stop receiving communications from the Seller, he may opt out at any time by clicking on the opt out link inside any one of our emails or: 

  * Emailing our Customer Service team at [privacy@beyondtherack.com](mailto:privacy@beyondtherack.com), or

  * Calling our toll-free number at 1-844-400-4287 Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET, or

  * Mailing to:

Privacy Matters  
c/o Beyond the Rack   
5440 Pare,  
Mont-Royal, Quebec  
H4P 1R3, Canada

**19\. Invite-A-Friend**

BTR uses SociableLabs to operate our referral program. Notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, Personal Information may be securely transferred to SociableLabs or other third parties in the context of the referral program, but only to the extent needed for the referral program to operate properly. This transfer of Personal Information is described in the next paragraph of this section. By using the referral program, you consent to our use of your Personal Information in this manner. If you do not consent to the use of your Personal Information in this manner, please do not use the referral program.  
  
The referral program will access your web-based email service (currently limited to Gmail, Hotmail, Yahoo or AOL). If you are not otherwise logged-in to the email service, it may ask you for your password in order to log in.Your password is not stored by either us or SociableLabs, and is only transferred securely to your email provider in order to log in for the referral program to function. The referral program will access your contacts from your email program, and may ask for your authorization to do so. No emails are sent to your contacts without your consent, as you must confirm to which email addresses you send a referral. Use of your email service is also governed by your email provider’s Terms of Use and / or Privacy Policy.  
  
When you share a link through the referral program via Facebook or Twitter, if you are not otherwise logged in, you may be asked for your login information, and your login information is transferred securely to those services. Your use of these services is covered by their respective Terms of Use and / or Privacy Policies.  
  
BTR and SociableLabs are in full compliance with both the U.S. CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (15 U.S.C. Ch. 103) and the Canadian law Informally known as Canada’s Anti-Spam Law (“CASL”, S.C. 2010, c. 23) within the referral program. BTR As part of our referral program, emails are sent which are subject to anti-spam laws, including the U.S. CAN-SPAM Act and Canada’s Anti-Spam Law. As these laws have different requirements based on the email recipient’s home country, it is important to distinguish your recipients. By using the referral program, you acknowledge that if you are using the American version of the website and referral program, you are sending to American recipients. If you are using the Canadian version of the website and referral program, you are sending to Canadian recipients.  
  
If you believe you have been sent an email in error or in violation of these laws OR your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database by either:   
  
Making the necessary changes in your member information page, or   
  
Emailing our Customer Service team at [service@beyondtherack.com](mailto:service@beyondtherack.com), or   
  
Calling our toll-free number at 1-844-400-4287 Monday - Friday from 9AM - 5PM ET, or   
  
Mailing to: 

Privacy Matters  
c/o Beyond the Rack   
5440 Pare,  
Mont-Royal, Quebec  
H4P 1R3, Canada  
  
Furthermore you can prevent any future referral emails from BTR by clicking the unsubscribe link in any invitation email you received. 

**20\. BTR Travel Services**

**TERMS AND CONDITIONS – IMPORTANT INFORMATION REGARDING YOUR TRAVEL RESERVATIONS AND DOCUMENT REQUIREMENTS**

Beyond The Rack Travel, represented by Transat Distribution Canada Inc., a Quebec licensee (“TDC”), acts as an intermediary between you and your selected carriers, hotels, tour organizers, tour operators and other service providers (the “Service Providers”). Consequently, TDC can under no circumstances be held liable to you or your travel companions for the travel services rendered by said Service Providers (the “Travel Services”). TDC, in its capacity as travel agent, assumes no liability for Service Providers’ failure to perform their obligations, including but not limited to, for any damage or loss resulting from delay, cancellation, property loss, illness, injury, accident, death, quality of services, inconvenience, loss of enjoyment, disappointment or any event amounting to an act of God or force majeure. 

**PAYMENT TERMS AND CONDITIONS**

All Travel Services must be paid in full at the time of reservation with TDC and these Travel Services are non-transferable and non-refundable. You are responsible for verifying the terms and conditions in the brochure of the Service Providers corresponding to the Travel Services purchased. Some airline tickets are issued at a special rate that carries restrictions. In the event of any discrepancy between these terms and conditions and those of any Service Providers or those stated in the beyondtherack.com website, the terms and conditions stated herein shall prevail. If full payment is not received or not honored by our credit card processor or financial institution, TDC reserves the right to cancel your reservation without notice and without reimbursement. Travel insurance must also be paid in full at the time of reservation. In the event of a cancellation of any Travel Services purchased from TDC prior to departure, TDC will keep 100% of the total cost of such cancelled Travel Service received from you. If you request a change to any Travel Services, TDC or the Service Providers may allow, at their discretion, such change subject to the payment of certain change fees. If such change to your Travel Services is not allowed or you choose not to travel or use the Travel Services purchased, a cancellation fee equal to 100% of the total cost of the Travel Service will be charged by TDC. Please contact TDC at 1-866-815-5196 with respect to any change request. 

**TRAVEL DOCUMENTS**

It is your entire responsibility to obtain, at your own expense, all required travel documents (including but not limited to passport, visa, tourist card, permanent resident card, official documents) and to abide by the laws in place at your travel destinations. TDC cannot be held liable for any damages resulting from failure to obtain travel documents or any delay which you may experience in obtaining such documents. TDC advises consumers to visit the website of the Department of Foreign Affairs and International Trade at the following address: www.dfait.gc.ca. The site provides information and assistance for Canadians travelling abroad. Travel document requirements are subject to change; you are advised to check for such changes prior to your travel. 

**FOR U.S. AND INTERNATIONAL TRAVEL**

A Canadian passport is required; some countries require up to 6 months validity beyond your anticipated stay and a visa may be required; check with your travel agent. Recommended check-in time is at least 2 hours (for U.S. travel) or 3 hours (for international travel) prior to departure. Failure to check in at least 60 minutes prior may result in cancellation of your reservation or advanced seat assignment. Please re¬confirm all international flights 24 hours prior to departure directly with the airline. Living standards and practices in other countries, and the conditions there with respect to the provision of utilities, services and accommodations, may differ greatly from those found in Canada and the United States. A previous criminal record could be an obstacle in U.S. and international travel leading to denied entry. Medical inoculations may be recommended depending on the country or region to which you are travelling. 

**CHILDREN**

If a minor (i.e. under 18) is travelling with only one parent, either (i) the absent parent must provide notarized consent or (ii) the travelling parent must provide proof of sole custody or a notarized letter that the other parent is deceased, as the case may be. All notarized consent letters should indicate the destination and length of travel, as well as consent to provide emergency medical treatment if required. If a minor is travelling alone or is accompanied by an adult other than a parent, both parents (or the sole documented custodial parent) must provide notarized consent. If a minor travelling alone has only one parent as evidenced by its birth certificate, a notarized copy of the birth certificate or the original together with the notarized consent of the parent will be sufficient proof allowing for travel. If a minor child travelling alone has only one parent due to the death of the other parent, the notarized consent of the custodial parent is required. 

**INSURANCE**

For each reservation, TDC offers you and your travel companions the option of taking out an insurance policy to protect you and your travel companions against certain events – including but not limited to coverage for trip cancellation or interruption, out of country medical, travel accident, baggage, personal effects, personal money, travel delay, etc. – that may occur before, during or after (for a specified number of weeks) your trip. You hereby acknowledge that TDC made this offer of insurance in good faith and that you have made an informed decision to take out or refuse such insurance and to assume full liability for your decision. 

**WAIVER AND RELEASE**

You hereby acknowledge and agree that TDC will not be liable or responsible for any losses incurred by you or your travel companions resulting from denied boarding of an aircraft, vessel or any other mode of transportation, for unsatisfactory trip conditions or for any other matter relating to the trip. You and your travel companions hereby release TDC and its directors, officers, agents, employees from any liability or claim that your or your travel companions now have or may ever have relating to the your trip. 

**COMPLIANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS**

By reserving travel services, you are deemed to have accepted the above terms and conditions and you are expressly acknowledging that TDC has sufficiently advised you in respect of the above listed matters.   

Transat Distribution Canada Inc., representing Beyond The Rack Travel, is registered as a travel retailer in Quebec (#753141), Ontario (# 50015084) and British Columbia (# 23567) with offices at: Place du Parc, 300 Léo-Pariseau, Suite 1601, Montreal (Quebec) H2X 4B3; 191 The West Mall, Suite 700, Etobicoke (Ontario) M9C 5K8; and Park Royal Shopping Centre, 2009 Park Royal South, West Vancouver (British Columbia) V7T 1A1.
